Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 10: Concert Recordings, 252 boxes (266.2 linear ft.)
  - Audio Open Reel Tapes and Cassettes
    - Concert Recordings 7610-7620:, 02-14-1976 -- 04-28-1976; 19 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 433)
      (7612:1-2) Alexander Slobodianik [Aleksander Slobodyanik], piano, 03-09-1976: Mi︠a︡skovskiĭ, N. (Nikolaĭ), 1881-1950. Sonatas, piano, no. 4, op. 27, C minor -- Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Kont︠s︡ertnoe allegro -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 8, op. 13, C minor -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Ballades, piano, no. 4, op. 52, F minor -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Scherzos, piano, no. 1, op. 20, B minor -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Episoden aus Lenau's Faust. Tanz in der Dorfschenke; arr.
      (7613:1-2) Alexis Weissenberg, piano, 03-14-1976: Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Chromatische Fantasie und Fuge -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Fantasien, piano, op. 17, C major -- Mussorgsky, Modest Petrovich, 1839-1881. Kartinki s vystavki
      (7614:1-2) Berlin Philharmonic Octet, 03-15-1976: Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Sonatas, violins (2), violoncello, double bass. No. 3 -- Hindemith, Paul, 1895-1963. Octet, woodwinds, horn, strings -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Septet, woodwinds, horn, strings, op. 20, E♭ major
      (7615) Cleo Laine, vocalist, with John Dankworth, 03-21-1976: Dankworth, John. Songs. Selections [Dankworth’s jazz compositions, featuring the verse of William Shakespeare and other authors set to music, along with arrangements of works by other composers. All titles from program:] Prologue, all the world’s a stage -- If musick be the food of love -- As an imperfeck actor -- O mistress mine -- Shall I compare thee to a summer’s day -- It was a lover and his lass -- Compleat works -- Lines to R. Hodgson, Esq. -- Goe and catche a falling starre -- Dr. David Mantle -- Teeth -- Song -- Phone conversation from Sweeney Agonistes -- Thieving boy -- Tell me the truth about love -- Sing me no song -- Modest heart -- Sun, the moon and I -- Greatest man -- You do something to me -- Mad about the boy -- Matelot -- There are bad times -- London pride -- Blow, blow thou winter wind -- Who is Sylvia? -- Take all my loves -- You spotted snakes -- Dunsinane blues -- Epilogue: Our revels now are ended
      (7616:1-2) John Browning, piano, 03-25-1976: Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Sonatas, piano, D. 959, A major -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Études-tableaux, op. 33. Selections -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Gaspard de la nuit
      (7617:1-2) Michel Beroff, piano, 04-06-1976: Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Humoresque, piano, op. 20, B♭ major -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Gaspard de la nuit -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Etudes, piano. Selections -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Preludes, piano, book 1. Cathédrale engloutie -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Preludes, piano, book 1. Sérénade interrompue -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Preludes, piano, book 2. Feux d'artifice -- Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992. Preludes, piano (1929). Selections -- Messiaen, Olivier, 1908-1992. Vingt regards sur l'Enfant Jésus. Selections
      (7618:1-2) Cleveland Quartet, 04-11-1976: Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Quartets, strings, no. 1, op. 50, B minor -- Hoffstetter, Roman, 1742-1815. Quartets, strings, op. 3. No. 5 [not composed by Haydn] -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Quartets, strings, no. 13, op. 130, B♭ major
      (7620:1-2) Shirley Verrett, mezzo-soprano; Warren Wilson, piano, 04-28-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7621:1), Box 583]
      Slobodi︠a︡nik, Aleksandr; Weissenberg, Alexis; Tretʹi︠a︡kov, Viktor; Philharmonisches Oktett Berlin; Cleveland Quartet; Laine, Cleo; Browning, John, 1933-2003; Béroff, Michel; Verrett, Shirley
    - Concert Recordings 7621-7631:, 05-16-1976 -- 12-07-1976; 19 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 434)
      (7621:1-2) Mona Golabek, piano, 05-16-1976: Bartók, Béla, 1881-1945. Suites, piano, op. 14 -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 21, op. 53, C major -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Scherzos, piano, no. 2, op. 31, B♭ minor -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Mazurkas, piano, op. 24. Selections -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Nocturnes, piano, op. 9. No. 3 -- Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Sonatas, piano, no. 5, op. 53
      (7622:1-2) Earl Wrightson, baritone; Lois Hunt, soprano; “On the Lighter Side,” 10-02-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7624:1), Box 583]
      (7623:1-2) Musica Da Camera of Prague, 10-14-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7625:1), Box 583]
      (7624:1-2) Tokyo Symphony Orchestra; Kazuyoshi Akiyama, conductor, 10-16-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7626:1), Box 583]
      (7625:2) Tokyo Symphony Orchestra; Kazuyoshi Akiyama, conductor, 10-17-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7627:1), Box 583]
      (7626:1-2) Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 10-21-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7628:1), Box 584]
      (7627:1-2) Gérard Souzay, baritone; Dalton Baldwin, piano, 10-23-1976: [see also Tape (7629:1), Box 584] Peri, Jacopo, 1561-1633. [Title from program:] O miei giorni fugaci -- Quagliati, Paolo, ca. 1555-1628. [Title from program:] Apre il suo verde seno -- Calestani, Vincenzo, 1589-1617. [Title from program:] Ferma, Dorinda mia -- Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725. Pompeo. Toglietemi la vita ancor -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Chanson de printemps -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Viens, les gazons sont verts -- Duparc, Henri, 1848-1933. Manoir de Rosemond -- Duparc, Henri, 1848-1933. Soupir -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Romanzen und Lieder, op. 84. Vergebliches Ständchen -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Gesänge, op. 7. Parole -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Gesänge, op. 43. Mainacht -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 47. O liebliche Wangen -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Mélodies populaires grecques -- Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Don Quichotte à Dulcinée. Chanson à boire -- Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946. Canciones populares españolas. Selections
      (7629:1-2) Music from Marlboro: Pina Carmirelli, violin; Jerry Grossman, cello; Doris Lederer, viola; Philipp Naegele, viola; Marcy Rosen, cello; Naoko Tanaka, violin, 11-11-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7633:1), Box 585]
      (7630:1-2) Salvatore Accardo, violin; unidentified pianist, 11-21-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7634:1), Box 585]
      (7631:1-2) Murray Perahia, piano, 12-07-1976: [for program information, see Tape (7635:1), Box 585]
      Perahia, Murray; Hunt, Lois; Wrightson, Earl; Musica da camera Praga; Tōkyō Kōkyō Gakudan; Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center; Souzay, Gérard; Golabek, Mona; Musicians from Marlboro; Accardo, Salvatore
    - Concert Recordings 7632-7709:, 12-12-1976 -- 02-08-1977; 20 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 435)
      (7632:1-2) Gary Graffman, piano, 12-12-1976: [see also Tape (7636:1), Box 585] Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Sonatas, piano, D. 958, C minor -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Variationen über ein Thema von Paganini -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Sonatas, piano, no. 3, op. 28, A minor -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Preludes, piano, op. 32. No. 5 -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Preludes, piano, op. 32. No. 8 -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Morceaux de salon, piano. Barcarolle -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Études-tableaux, op. 39. No 5 -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Études-tableaux, op. 33. No 2 -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Études-tableaux, op. 39. No 4
      (7701:1-2) Bronislaw Gimpel, violin; Jakob Gimpel, piano, 01-08-1977: [Program from listing on cassette container; see also Tapes (7701:1-2), Box 435] Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 8, op. 30, no. 3, G major -- Franck, César, 1822-1890. Sonatas, violin, piano, A major
      (7702:1-2) Tedd Joselson, piano, 01-09-1977: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 6, op. 10, no. 2, F major -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Sonatas, piano, no. 8, op. 84, B♭ major -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Chromatische Fantasie und Fuge -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Konzertetüden. Waldesrauschen -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Consolations. No 3 -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Études d'exécution transcendante. No 10, F minor
      (7703:1-2) Alfons Kontarsky and Aloys Kontarsky, pianos, 01-16-1977: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Fugues, pianos (2), K. 426, C minor -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Larghetto und Allegro, pianos (2), E♭ major -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, pianos (2), op. 34b, F minor -- Reger, Max, 1873-1916. Variationen und Fuge über ein Thema von Beethoven
      (7704:1-2) Yong Uck Kim, violin; David Oei, piano, 01-22-1977: Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Sonatas, violin, piano, D. 574, A major -- Webern, Anton, 1883-1945. Stücke, violin, piano, op. 7 -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Rondeau brillant, violin, piano -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Sonatas, violin, piano, op. 18, E♭ major -- Suk, Josef, 1874-1935. Skladby, violin, piano, op. 17. Poco triste -- Suk, Josef, 1874-1935. Skladby, violin, piano, op. 17. Burleska
      (7705:1-2) Catherine Malfitano, soprano; Lawrence Skrobacs, piano, 01-23-1977: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Exsultate, jubilate -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Fêtes galantes, 1. Recueil -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 47. Botschaft -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 47. Sonntag -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Lieder, op. 105. Immer leiser wird mein Schlummer -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Gesänge, op. 43. Von ewiger Liebe -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Malinconia, ninfa gentile -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Bella Nice che d'amore -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Una voce poco fa -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Hermit songs
      (7706:1-2) Daniel Shafran, violoncello; Anton Ginzburg, piano, 01-27-1977: Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, no. 1, op. 38, E minor -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Sonatas, arpeggione, piano, D. 821, A minor -- Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975. Sonatas, viola, piano, op. 147; arr.
      (7707:1-2) Oscar Brand, folksinger, 01-29-1977: [no program listed]
      (7708:1-2) Christiane Edinger, violin; Gerhard Puchelt, piano, 02-05-1977: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, violin, piano, no. 5, op. 24, F major -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Sonaten und Partiten, violin, BWV 1001-1006. Sonata, no. 1 -- Einem, Gottfried von, 1918-1996. Sonatas, violin, op. 47 -- Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Sonatas, flute, piano, op. 94, D major; arr.
      (7709:1-2) Eastman Quartet, 02-08-1977: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Quintets, piano, oboe, clarinet, horn, bassoon, op. 16, E♭ major; arr. -- Martinů, Bohuslav, 1890-1959. Quartets, piano, strings -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Quartets, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 25, G minor
      Kontarsky, Alfons; Eastman Quartet; Gimpel, Bronislav; Kim, Young Uck; Kontarsky, Aloys; Joselson, Tedd; Brand, Oscar; Gimpel, Jakob; Malfitano, Catherine; Edinger, Christiane; Graffman, Gary; Shafran, Daniil
    - Concert Recordings 7710-7717:, 02-09-1977 -- 06-06-1977; 16 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 436)
      (7710:1-2) Chamber Orchestra of Prague; Hans Richter-Haaser, piano, 02-09-1977: Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Introduction und Allegro appassionato -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Concertos, piano, orchestra, no. 2, op. 19, B♭ major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Concertos, piano, orchestra, K. 467, C major -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Symphonies, K. 297, D major
      (7711:1-2) Nicanor Zabaleta, harp, 02-10-1977: Cabezón, Antonio de, 1510-1566. Pavana con su glosa; arr. -- Rosetti, Antonio, ca. 1750-1792. Sonatas, keyboard instrument, M. D20, E♭ major -- Corelli, Arcangelo, 1653-1713. Sonatas, violin, continuo, op. 5. No. 7; arr. -- Samuel-Rousseau, Marcel, 1882-1955. Variations pastorales sur un vieux noël -- Bacarisse, Salvador, 1898-1963. Partita, harp -- José Antonio de Donostia. Preludios vascos, piano. Selections; arr. -- Albéniz, Mateo, d. 1831. Sonata, piano, D major; arr. -- Halffter, Ernesto, 1905-1989. Sonatina. Danza de la pastora -- Salzedo, Carlos, 1885-1961. Method for the harp. Désirade -- Salzedo, Carlos, 1885-1961. Method for the harp. Chanson dans la nuit
      (7712:1-2) Claudio Arrau, piano, 02-13-1977: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 30, op. 109, E major -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Sonata, piano, B minor -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, piano, no. 3, op. 5, F minor
      (7713:1-2) Mstislav Rostropovich, violoncello; Samuel Sanders, piano, 02-23-1977: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. [unidentified aria, arranged] -- Weber, Carl Maria von, 1786-1826. Sonates progressives. No 2. Adagio; arr. -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, no. 2, op. 99, F major -- Shostakovich, Dmitriĭ Dmitrievich, 1906-1975. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, op. 40
      (7714:1-2) Igor Kipnis, harpsichord, 03-05-1977, one box contains a concert program: Marchand, Louis, 1669-1732. Pièces de clavecin, 1er livre -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Partitas, harpsichord, BWV 827, A minor -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 322, A major -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 323, A major -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 443, D major -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 444, D minor -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 337, G major -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 338, G major -- Scarlatti, Domenico, 1685-1757. Sonatas, harpsichord, K. 146, G major
      (7715:1-2) Pasadena Community Orchestra; R. Gerry Long, conductor; Supersax, 05-08-1977, one box contains a concert program: Prokofiev, Sergey, 1891-1953. Poruchik Kizhe. Suite -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Solomon. Sinfonia -- Long, R. Gerry. Saxophone rondo -- Dubois, Pierre Max, 1930-1995. Concertos, saxophone, string orchestra -- Worrall, Tom. Sketches, saxophones, orchestra -- Kern, Jerome, 1885-1945. Very warm for May. All the things you are; arr. -- Robin, Leo. If I should lose you; arr. -- Duke, Vernon, 1903-1969. Walk a little faster. April in Paris, arr. -- Rodgers, Richard, 1902-1979. Too many girls. I didn't know what time it was; arr.
      (7716:1-2) Marvellee Cariaga, mezzo-soprano; Daniel Cariaga, piano, 05-10-1977: Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Ombra mai fù; arr. -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Clemenza di Tito. Parto, ma tu ben mio; arr. -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Songs. Selections -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Ma dall' arido stelo divulsa; arr. -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Songs. Selections -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Samson et Dalila. Mon cœur s'ouvre à ta voix; arr. -- Barber, Samuel, 1910-1981. Hermit songs. Selections -- Frackenpohl, Arthur Roland, 1924- Recent rulings -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Selections; arr.
      (7717:1-2) Pasadena Community Orchestra, 06-06-1977: Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Fidelio (1806). Ouverture -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Divertimenti, K. 131, D major. Selections -- Khachaturi︠a︡n, Aram Ilʹich, 1903-1978. Maskarad. Suite -- Babajanyan, Aṛno, 1921-1983. Herosakan ballad -- Nelson, Ron, 1929- Jubilee
      Zabaleta, Nicanor; Kipnis, Igor; Arrau, Claudio; Rostropovich, Mstislav; Pražský komorní orchestr; Long, R. Gerry; Supersax (Musical group); Cariaga, Marvellee
    - Concert Recordings 7718-7724:, 10-01-1977 -- 11-22-1977; 14 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 437)
      (7718:1-2) Carlos Montoya, guitar, 10-01-1977, one box contains a concert program: Zapateao -- Huelva -- Nana del gitanito -- Levante -- Chufla -- Rondeña -- Alegrías en dos tonos -- Toque de cana y soleá -- Guajiras -- Canción del norte y Mallorca -- Aires de genil -- Jota -- Tango antiguo -- Zambra -- Granaina -- Variaciones -- Málaga
      (7719:1-3) Carlos Montoya guitar, 10-01-1977, one box contains a concert program: [for program information, see Tapes (7718:1-2) above]
      (7720:1-2) An evening with Dame Alicia Markova and Anton Dolin and Friends, hosted by Walter Terry, 10-16-1977: Walter Terry spotlights the art of Markova and Dolin, illustrating their greatest roles with picture slides -- Mr. Terry interviews Dame Alicia and Mr. Dolin and discusses their unique joint careers -- Dame Alicia and Mr. Dolin offer mimed excerpts from Swan Lake, Act II -- Dame Alicia and Mr. Dolin teach two Southern California dancers, Elizabeth Hall and Douglas Davis, the Adagio from Swan Lake, Act II -- Dame Alicia and Mr. Dolin recreate mimed excerpts from Giselle, perhaps their greatest roles
      (7721:1-2) Dolmetsch/Schoenfeld [Carl Dolmetsch, recorder; Joseph Saxby, harpsichord; Alice Schoenfeld, violin; Eleonore Schoenfeld, violoncello], 10-18-1977, one box contains a concert program: Telemann, Georg Philipp, 1681-1767. Trio sonata in A major [unspecified] -- Nardini, Pietro, 1722-1793. Sonatas, violin, continuo, op. 2. No. 5, D major -- Marais, Marin, 1656-1728. Pièces de violes, 2e livre. Selections -- Leclair, Jean-Marie, 1697-1764. Trio sonatas, violins, continuo, op. 4. No. 3 -- Kodály, Zoltán, 1882-1967. Duet, violin, violoncello, op. 7 -- Bernard, Emile, 1843-1902. Prelude and scherzo -- Jacob, Gordon, 1895-1984. Suites, recorder, string orchestra. Tarantella; arr. -- Cooke, Arnold. Sonatas, harpsichord, recorder, strings
      (7722:1-2) Julian Bream, lute and guitar, 10-27-1977, one box contains a concert program: Francesco, da Milano, 1497-1543. Fantasias, lute. Selections -- Dowland, John, 1563?-1626. Loth to departe -- Milán, Luis, 16th cent. Maestro. Selections -- Milán, Luis, 16th cent. Maestro. Tento [unspecified] -- Cutting, Francis. Divisions on Walsingham -- Cutting, Francis. Lute music. Selections -- Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Präludium, Fuge und Allegro, lute, BWV 998, E♭ major; arr. -- Giuliani, Mauro, 1781-1829. Grande ouverture -- Bennett, Richard Rodney. Impromptus, guitar -- Albéniz, Isaac, 1860-1909. Suite española, no. 1. Selections
      (7723:2, 2-track) Luciano Pavarotti, tenor; John Wustman, piano, 11-06-1977: Giordani, Giuseppe, 1751-1798. Caro mio ben -- Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Orfeo ed Euridice. Che farò senza Euridice -- Legrenzi, Giovanni, 1626-1690. Eteocle e Polinice. Che fiero costume -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. In questa tomba oscura -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Nuits d’été à Pausilippe. Barcajuolo -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Soirées musicales. Danza -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. De' miei bollenti spiriti -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Années de pèlerinage, 2e année. Sonetto 47 del Petrarca -- Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Années de pèlerinage, 2e année. Sonetto 104 del Petrarca -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. Fra poco a me ricovero -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Good-bye -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Aprile -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Ideale -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Marechiare
      (7724:1-2, 2-track) Gerhard Oppitz, piano, 11-22-1977: Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Variationen über ein eigenes Thema -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, piano, no. 32, op. 111, C minor -- Scriabin, Aleksandr Nikolayevich, 1872-1915. Sonatas, piano, no. 5, op. 53 -- Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849. Polonaise-fantaisie
      Dolmetsch-Schoenfeld Ensemble; Bream, Julian; Schoenfeld, Eleanore; Dolin, Anton; Dolmetsch, Carl F.; Saxby, Joseph, 1910-1997; Montoya, Carlos; Schoenfeld, Alice; Markova, Alicia, Dame; Pavarotti, Luciano; Oppitz, Gerhard
    - Concert Recordings 7725-7806:, 11-28-1977 -- 03-02-1978; 14 10 1/2" open reel tapes, 2 track (Box 438)
      (7725:2) Mstislav Rostropovich, violoncello; Samuel Sanders, piano, 11-28-1977: Marcello, Benedetto, 1686-1739. Adagio [unspecified] -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Fantasiestücke, clarinet, piano; arr. -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, no. 2, op. 5, no. 2, G minor -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Sonatas, violoncello, piano, op. 6, F major -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Sonatas, violoncello, piano
      (7726:1) Hank Aaron, speaker (lecture series), 11-30-1977: [box contains a program]
      (7801:1-2) Régine Crespin, soprano; John Wustman, piano, 01-28-1978: Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886. Songs. Selections -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Songs. Selections -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Goethe-Lieder. Anakreons Grab -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Goethe-Lieder. Mignon -- Chabrier, Emmanuel, 1841-1894. Mélodies (1890). Île heureuse -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Noël des enfants qui n'ont plus de maisons -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Mélodies (1855). Venise -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Amoreuse -- Guastavino, Carlos, 1912-2000. Rosa y el sauce -- Guridi, Jesús, 1886-1961. Canciones castellanas. No quiero tus avellanas -- Guridi, Jesús, 1886-1961. Canciones castellanas. Cómo quieres que adivine -- Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Périchole. Ah, quel dîner! -- Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Grande duchesse de Gérolstein. Ah! que j'aime les militaries
      (7802:2) Andre Watts, piano, 02-02-1978: [for program information, see Tape (7803:1), Box 575; see also Tape (7803:2), Box 447, and Tape (7802:1), Box 553]
      (7802/A:1-2) Karan Armstrong, soprano; Russell Stepan, piano, 02-04-1978: Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Come scoglio -- Marx, Joseph, 1882-1964. Lieder und Gesänge. Valse de Chopin -- Marx, Joseph, 1882-1964. Lieder und Gesänge. Hat dich die Liebe berührt -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly. Tu, tu, piccolo iddio -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. À sa guitar -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Banalités. Hôtel -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Léocadia. Chemins de l'amour -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. Dich, teure Halle -- Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Arlesiana. No è malato -- Obradors, Fernando J. Songs. Selections -- Niles, John Jacob, 1892-1980. He’s gone away -- Niles, John Jacob, 1892-1980. Black is the color of my true love's hair -- Sieczyński, Rudolf, 1879-1952. Wien, du Stadt meiner Träume -- Lehár, Franz, 1870-1948. Lustige Witwe. Lippen schweigen -- Lehár, Franz, 1870-1948. Lustige Witwe. Es lebt' eine Vilja
      (7803:2) Pearl Bailey, entertainer (lecture series), 02-09-1978
      (7804:1-2) Carlo Bergonzi, tenor; John Wustman, piano, 02-16-1978: Scarlatti, Alessandro, 1660-1725. Honestà negli amori. Già il sole dal Gange -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Songs. Selections -- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827. Zärtliche Liebe -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Gedichte, op. 35. Wanderlied -- Pietri, Giuseppe, 1886-1946. Maristella. Io conosco un giardino -- Caccini, Giulio, 1551-1618. Nuove musiche. Amarilli mia bella -- Tirindelli, P. A. (Pier Adolfo), 1858-1937. O primavera! -- Donaudy, Stefano, 1879-1925. Arie di stile antico. O del mio amato ben -- Lalo, Edouard, 1823-1892. Roi d'Ys. Aubade -- Giordani, Giuseppe, 1751-1798. Caro mio ben -- De Crescenzo, Vincenzo, 1875-1964. Rondine al nido -- Halévy, F., 1799-1862. Juive. Rachel! quand du Seigneur la grâce tutélaire